http://www.nsbank.com/privacy/

Privacy and Security | Nevada State Bank
Compare0Clear All
You can compare maximum three products at a time. Please adjust the selection accordingly.
Compare
You can only compare three products at a time. Unselect an account or use clear all to start over.
Hide
Choose Your State
Rates and products offered may differ from state to state. To see the rate and offering available to you, please select the state where you bank. (Your privacy is important to us—see our Privacy Notice).
--- Choose Your State ---
Alabama
Alaska
Arizona
Arkansas
California
Colorado
Connecticut
Corporate Banking
HOW CAN WE HELP YOU?
Compare Checking Accounts
Compare Savings Accounts
Compare Credit Cards
Enroll in Online Banking
Sign Up for Bill Pay
Go Paperless with eDocuments
Learn About Mobile Banking
Explore Wealth Management Options
Digital Payments
HOW CAN WE HELP YOU?
Buy or Refinance a Home
Consolidate My Debt
Buy or Refinance a Vehicle
Compare Mortgage Loan Rates & Options
Compare Mortgage Refinancing Options
Compare Home Equity Credit Line Rates & Options
LET'S GET STARTED
Find a Mortgage Officer
Global Banking
HOW CAN WE HELP YOU?
Compare Checking Accounts
Compare Savings Accounts
Compare Credit Cards
Enroll in Online Banking
Sign Up for Bill Pay
Learn About Mobile Banking
Explore Business Banking Services
Explore Wealth Management Options
Commercial Card
HOW CAN WE HELP YOU?
Learn More About SBA Loans
Finance a Building
Purchase or Finance Equipment
Learn About Factoring
LET'S GET STARTED
Schedule an Appointment
Let Us Contact You
Find a Business Center
Zero Balance Accounts
HOW CAN WE HELP YOU?
Help Minimize Fraud Risk
Make Payments with Ease
Collect Receivables More Efficiently
Access Account Info in a Timely Manner
Make the Most of My Excess Cash Flow
LET'S GET STARTED
Schedule an Appointment
Let Us Contact You
Search the website
What Can We Help You Find?
Login
PRIVACY & SECURITY
We value your trust and respect your privacy
Identity Theft & Internet Fraud
Get more information on identity theft and Internet fraud, and find out what you can do to help protect yourself. Learn more about Identity theft and Internet fraud.
Privacy Notice
At Nevada State Bank we take the privacy of your information seriously. We encourage you to learn more about how we handle your information by reading our privacy notice. For more information, please review the Nevada State Bank Privacy Notice and Online Privacy Statement.
Online Banking Security - To help protect your online security, please use the following tips when accessing your Online Banking account:
To use Online Banking, you must use a 128 bit encrypted secured browser, such as Internet Explorer version 8.0 or newer. Get Microsoft® Internet Explorer today!
Nevada State Bank uses a unique Online User Name which serves as your identifier when using Online Banking. We also require the use of a Secret Password that you can change at your convenience. Those using our Business Online Banking service also have a unique Company ID. When accessing your Online Banking account, take these simple steps to help verify you are on the authentic Nevada State Bank website, www.nsbank.com.
Always access the Online Banking website by manually typing in the URL https://www.nsbank.com or by using a preconfigured bookmark pointing to https://www.nsbank.com. It is a good practice to avoid accessing your accounts by clicking on links on other websites or in emails.
Once you have accessed the Online Banking website, validate that the URL in the address bar is https://www.nsbank.com.
Look for your browser’s symbol indicating that you are on a secured website whose authenticity has been verified by an independent authority. For example, in Internet Explorer, a padlock image will appear to the right of the address line. You can view the details of the authenticity by clicking on the lock.
For technical information about Online Banking, please refer to our FAQs page.
Final Note
Please keep your Nevada State Bank Online User Name and Password secret. If you feel either may have been lost or compromised, please notify Nevada State Bank Online Banking Support immediately at 1-888-835-0551. Remember! A Nevada State Bank employee will NEVER ask you for your Online Banking password. If you have further questions about security when using Online Banking, please contact Online Banking Support at 1-888-835-0551.
Disclosures
PRIVACY & SECURITY
Identity Theft & Internet Fraud
CONTACT US
Call
800.727.4743
ALL CONTACT INFO
FIND A BRANCH
Follow us on:
Nevada State Bank, a division of Zions Bancorporation, N.A. Member FDIC |  Equal Housing Lender | NMLS #467014
Data Collection and Rights | Do Not Sell My Personal Information
© 2020 Zions Bancorporation, N.A. All rights reserved.
